35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous], 1949, circa 1970s; 4 (Box 1584)
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another man (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?) beside indoor swimming pool], 3
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas], 4
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas], 5
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas in a golf cart], 6
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas in a golf cart], 7
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas in a golf cart], 8
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas in a golf cart with their dog], 9
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: The Potala Palace], 10
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another man (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?) beside the indoor pool], 11
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas, Sr. and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with Tibetan people, the Potala Palace in the background], 12
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with a man and a woman out on a patio], 13
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man holding a pet monkey out on patio], 14
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Young woman sitting on patio], 15
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?) with Frances Ryan Thomas in golf cart], 16
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another woman sitting out on patio], 17
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?) and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a golf cart], 18
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of men together for a picture, Lowell Thomas fourth from left], 19
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of men together for a picture, Lowell Thomas fourth from left], 20
  - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous], 1949, circa 1970s; 5 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: People sitting outside at tables, listening to a man play the guitar], 1
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas getting a drink], 2
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Poster for "Oral Roberts in Alaska"], 3
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of people outside, man (Richard Nixon?) pouring a drink, Lowell Thomas standing next to him], 4
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men], 5
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Some people sitting at a table, eating], 6
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man (Richard Nixon) making a drink, Lowell Thomas next to him], 7
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with two other men (Richard Nixon?)], 8
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: People sitting outside at tables, listening to a man play the guitar], 9
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: People seated at a table with Richard Nixon?], 10
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: People putting on a performance], 11
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Two people singing], 12
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of a map], 13
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of a map], 14
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting at microphone in front of world map], 15
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas talking with two other men in his broadcasting office], 16
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man standing by lighting equipment], 17
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Musical group giving a performance], 18
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man reclining in chair], 19
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man in fur coat, standing in front of snowy mountain], 20
  - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous], 1949, circa 1970s; 6 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women sitting around table], 1
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women seated around table], 2
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women seated around table], 3
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women seated around table], 4
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women seated around table], 5
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Woman outside, petting a dog], 6
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Man and woman raising the American flag], 7
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women sitting around a table], 8
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Group of women sitting around a table], 9
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Woman holding pet dog], 10
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Farm house at the bottom of a hill], 11
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Farm house at the bottom of a hill], 12
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]:Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas looking over edge of a deck at a river, 13
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Large white hosue hidden behind trees], 14
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Aerial view of farm house], 15
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: River running by hills], 16
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas on a deck in front of river], 17
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Back of a white house], 18
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Aerial view of farm house], 19
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Aerial view of farm house], 20
  - Carousel number 6 [extended family], circa 1970s; 7 (Box 1584)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 6 [extended family] [Boy mounted on a white horse], 1
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Boy petting white horse], 2
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Boy mounted on horse], 3
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Boat tied to dock], 4
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man standing next to boat tied at dock], 5
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Boat tied to dock], 6
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman and man cutting cake], 7
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Close-up of man sitting in boat], 8
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: A pine tree], 9
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man holding a baby], 10
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman cutting cake], 11
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Potted plants in house], 12
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man and woman sitting together], 13
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man sitting in chair], 14
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Two men sitting on couch], 15
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Two men and two women standing together outside of house], 16
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Two men and two women standing together outside of house], 17
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Two men and two women standing together outside of house], 18
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Three men sitting on couch, baby sitting on man's lap], 19
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Cake that reads "Happy 25th Anniversary Lois and Dan"], 20
  - Carousel number 6 [extended family], circa 1970s; 8 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Three people sitting in chairs, little girl sitting on man's lap], 1
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Close-up of a man], 2
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man smiling], 3
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Little boy and older man holding a baby, sitting on a couch], 4
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Two men standing in a bathroom], 5
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Inside of an airport], 6
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Group of woman gathered, one opening a gift], 7
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman walking in house], 8
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]:Woman cutting anniversary cake], 9
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Inside of an airport], 10
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man and woman sitting outside together], 11
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Food laid out on a table], 12
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: People gathered together, having a party], 13
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man and woman talking], 14
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man putting food on his plate], 15
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Outdoor furniture on a deck], 16
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Garden decorations], 17
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: A garden], 18
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man lying on couch with a dog], 19
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: House], 20
  - Carousel number 6 [extended family] [Items 1-14] Carousel number 7 [Items 15-20], circa 1970s; 9 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Person holding a drink], 1
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Cooking meat on a grill], 2
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman standing in a kitchen], 3
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman sitting at a table outside, smoking], 4
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: People outside having a party], 5
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Person sitting in chair with a drink, outside], 6
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Close-up of a man in glasses, smiling], 7
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Strawberry shortcake cake], 8
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man smiling], 9
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: People sitting inside, talking], 10
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Little girl sitting on a chair, smiling], 11
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Woman wearing glasses, sitting], 12
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Man with little girl on his lap], 13
    - [Carousel number 6 [extended family]: Strawberry shortcake cake, graduation cake], 14
    - Beginning of Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship; [Lowell Thomas on golf course with his dog], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas with another man on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas with another man on golf course], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas driving a golf cart on his golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 10 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas and another man on golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas and another man on golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas sitting in golf cart with his dog], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas and another man on golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas and another man on golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on golf cart in the distance], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Trees on golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on golf cart], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on golf cart], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course during the winter], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course, trees, autumn], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course, trees], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course, and trees in autumn], 16